greydogsoftware.com 2006-06-19

# Grey Dog Software- Privacy Policy

Grey Dog Software Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. Grey Dog Software, LLC ("Grey Dog") makes every effort to keep your personal information confidential. We have strict procedures in place to ensure your information is protected. Below is our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, please contact the company's management team.

Grey Dog may collect personally identifying information from our users. Generally, this information is limited to name and e-mail address. Grey Dog does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card data, etc.) to any third parties under any circumstance. Grey Dog will occasionally contact individuals, in the form of newsletters and press announcements, using information that has been supplied to us, those who do not wish to be contacted should send an email to unsubscribe@greydogsoftware.com to specifically request that we remove you from our mailing list.   
Grey Dog uses cookies help track a person's activities while online, and are used mostly on our message forums. Cookies are not related to any personally identifiable information, and are not used to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Many browsers are set to accept cookies as a default. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse cookies. It is possible, however, that the message forums on this site will not function properly if you do so. 

Please note that this policy is effective as of September 1, 2004, and may be changed at any time, and at our discretion. Any changes to this policy will be announced by a member of the management team on the main page of the company's website. 

For information on the privacy policy of Viatech, Inc., please visit their website at [www.elicense.com](http://www.elicense.com/).
